<?xml version="1.0"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><title>Municipal Boundaries, Ramsey County, Minnesota</title><pubinfo><publish>Ramsey County Enterprise GIS</publish></pubinfo><pubdate>20190114</pubdate><origin>Ramsey County</origin><onlink>https://gisdata.mn.gov/dataset/us-mn-co-ramsey-bdry-admin-boundary-data</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>This dataset contains polygons that represent municipal boundaries.</abstract><purpose>Municipal boundaries support many functions including automated half and quarter section map production, thematic mapping, land records and property assessment and surveying and engineering projects.</purpose><supplinf>Ramsey County</supplinf></descript><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>As needed</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-93.228202</westbc><eastbc>-92.982974 </eastbc><northbc>45.124277</northbc><southbc>44.890922</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekey>boundaries, municipality, city, township</themekey><themekt>ISO Topic Category 19115</themekt></theme><place><placekey>Minnesota, MN, Ramsey County</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>None.</accconst><useconst>None. Please check sources, scale, accuracy, currentness and other available information. Please confirm that you are using the most recent copy of both data and metadata.  Acknowledgment of the publisher would be appreciated.</useconst><timeperd><timeinfo><sngdate><caldate>2018</caldate></sngdate></timeinfo><current>The dataset is current and complete, but regularly updated to reflect changes.  New versions are released monthly.</current></timeperd><browse><browsen>None Available</browsen></browse><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac></idinfo><distinfo><distliab>EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY STATED HEREIN, THIS DATA IS PROVIDED AS IS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. USER BEARS ANY AND ALL RISK RELATING TO QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THIS DATA. 
Limit on Liability:  This data is not a legally recorded map or survey and is not intended to be used as one. This data is a compilation of records and information from various state, county, and city offices, and other sources, and should be used for reference only.
In no event will the County of Ramsey be liable for direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages arising out of the use of, or inability to use, the data, even if advised of the possibility of such damages.  Specifically, the County of Ramsey is not responsible for any costs including, but not limited to, those incurred as a result of lost profits or revenue, loss of use of data, the costs of recovering such programs or data, the cost of any substitute programs or data, claims by third parties, or for other similar costs.</distliab><resdesc>ISvSQL75.GISWarehouse.Other.ADMIN_City</resdesc><stdorder><ordering>This data set is distributed on the internet by clicking below after Online Linkage.</ordering></stdorder><distrib><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20190114</metd><metstdn>Minnesota Geographic Metadata Guidelines</metstdn><metstdv>1.2</metstdv><metextns><onlink>http://www.mngeo.state.mn.us/committee/standards/mgmg/metadata.htm</onlink></metextns><metc><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></metc></metainfo><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>bdry_City</enttypl></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>CityID</attrlabl><attrdef>Number assigned based on alphabetical order of the city name</attrdef><attrdomv><rdom><rdommin>1</rdommin><rdommax>19</rdommax></rdom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>City</attrlabl><attrdef>Name of city</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>AScale</attrlabl><attrdef>Appropriate scale to fit municipality on A sized sheet</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>BScale</attrlabl><attrdef>Appropriate scale to fit municipality on B sized sheet</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>CScale</attrlabl><attrdef>Appropriate scale to fit municipality on C sized sheet</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>DScale</attrlabl><attrdef>Appropriate scale to fit municipality on D sized sheet</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>EScale</attrlabl><attrdef>Appropriate scale to fit municipality on E sized sheet</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>Orientation</attrlabl><attrdef>Appropriate orientation for fitting city to map sheet</attrdef><attrdomv><edom><edomv>L</edomv><edomvd>Landscape</edomvd></edom></attrdomv><attrdomv><edom><edomv>P</edomv><edomvd>Portrait</edomvd></edom></attrdomv></attr><attr><attrlabl>GNIS</attrlabl><attrdef>Geographic Names Information System Code</attrdef></attr></detailed></eainfo><dataqual><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>Digitized information is generally +/- 7 feet; some areas have been found to be +/- 30 feet.  COGO (coordinate geometry) accuracy generally is +/- 1.0 foot.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><attracc><attraccr>Attributes are populated from a compilation of records and information from various state, county and city offices, and other sources.  Accuracy may vary by source, but domains are used wherever possible to increase accuracy.</attraccr></attracc><complete>Entire Ramsey County coverage</complete><lineage><procstep><procdesc>The municipal [CITIES] boundaries were originally digitized from MNDOT municipality maps.  In 1995, the parcel data layer was converted to an ArcINFO format and held in an ArcStorm database.  Cities were converted in 2005 to an ESRI ArcGIS GeoDatabase.  

Over time, the municipal boundaries have been edited to better match the parcel data maintained by the county.</procdesc></procstep></lineage><logic>Information is visually inspected and corrected as necessary.</logic></dataqual><spref><horizsys><planar><gridsys><gridsysn>Universal Transverse Mercator</gridsysn><utm><utmzone>15</utmzone></utm></gridsys><planci><plandu>meters</plandu></planci></planar><geodetic><horizdn>NAD83</horizdn><ellips>GRS80</ellips></geodetic></horizsys></spref></metadata>