<?xml version="1.0"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>Ramsey County</origin><title>Administrative Boundaries, Ramsey County, Minnesota</title><pubinfo><publish>Ramsey County Enterprise GIS</publish></pubinfo><pubdate>20190628</pubdate><onlink>https://gisdata.mn.gov/dataset/us-mn-co-ramsey-bdry-admin-boundary-data</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>This file geodatabase contains datasets that represent municipal boundaries, commissioner district boundaries, precincts and park boundaries.

The following links can be used to obtain individual metadata pages: 

Municipal Boundaries:    &lt;a href="bdry_city.html"&gt;bdry_city.html&lt;/a&gt;
2012 County Commissioner Districts:    &lt;a href="bdry_commissionerdist2012.html"&gt;bdry_commissionerdist2012.html&lt;/a&gt;
Precinct Boundaries:    &lt;a href="bdry_precinct.html"&gt;bdry_precinct.html&lt;/a&gt; 
Park Boundaries:    &lt;a href="bdry_park.html"&gt;bdry_park.html&lt;/a&gt;
ECC Dispatch Areas:    &lt;a href="bdry_dispatcharea.html"&gt;bdry_dispatcharea.html&lt;/a&gt;</abstract><purpose>Administrative Boundaries support many functions including Ramsey Countys open data, automated half and quarter section map production, thematic mapping, land records and property assessment and surveying and engineering projects.</purpose><supplinf>Ramsey County</supplinf></descript><browse><browsen>None Available</browsen></browse><timeperd><current>Data set is current and complete, but updates vary. New versions are released monthly.

bdry_City:  content from 2018; maintenance and updates done as needed
bdry_CommissionerDist2012:  content from 2012; maintenance and updates happen following political re-districting activities
bdry_DispatchArea: the dataset is current and complete, but regularly updated to reflect changes
bdry_Park:  content from publication date; maintenance and updates are irregular
bdry_Precinct: content from publication date; maintenance and updates are irregular
</current><timeinfo><sngdate><caldate>Publication Date</caldate></sngdate></timeinfo></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>As needed</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-93.228202</westbc><eastbc>-92.982974 </eastbc><northbc>45.124277</northbc><southbc>44.890922</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><place><placekey>Minnesota, MN, Ramsey County</placekey></place><theme><themekt>ISO Topic Category 19115</themekt><themekey>boundaries, municipality, city, township, commissioner districts, county commissioners, political boundaries, parks, state park, regional park, county park, city park, open space, recreational center, golf course, computer aided dispatch areas, battalion, law enforcement, fire and emergency medical services, precinct</themekey></theme></keywords><accconst>None.</accconst><useconst>None. Please check sources, scale, accuracy, currentness and other available information. Please confirm that you are using the most recent copy of both data and metadata.  Acknowledgment of the publisher would be appreciated.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac></idinfo><dataqual><logic>Information is visually inspected and corrected as necessary.</logic><complete>Entire Ramsey County coverage</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>Digitized information is generally +/- 7 feet; some areas have been found to be +/- 30 feet. COGO (coordinate geometry) accuracy generally is +/- 1.0 foot.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>bdry_City: The Municipal [CITIES] boundaries were originally digitized from MNDOT municipality maps.  Over time, the boundaries have been edited to better match the parcel data maintained by the county.

bdry_CommissionerDist2012: The Ramsey County Commissioner Districts were created as part of a redistricting process following the 2010 census. 

bdry_DispatchAreas:  Created by Ramsey County Emergency Communications with consultation from the Public Safety agencies serving in Ramsey County.

bdry_Park: The parks boundaries are compiled from a variety of sources including Ramsey County Parks &amp; Recreation department and several municipalities.

bdry_Precinct: The Ramsey County Precincts were created as part of a redistricting process following the 2010 census and subsequent city resolutions.</procdesc></procstep></lineage><attracc><attraccr>Attributes are populated from a compilation of records and information from various state, county and city offices, and other sources.  Accuracy may vary by source, but domains are used wherever possible to increase accuracy.</attraccr></attracc></dataqual><distinfo><distliab>EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY STATED HEREIN, THIS DATA IS PROVIDED AS IS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. USER BEARS ANY AND ALL RISK RELATING TO QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THIS DATA. 
Limit on Liability:  This data is not a legally recorded map or survey and is not intended to be used as one. This data is a compilation of records and information from various state, county, and city offices, and other sources, and should be used for reference only.
In no event will the County of Ramsey be liable for direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages arising out of the use of, or inability to use, the data, even if advised of the possibility of such damages.  Specifically, the County of Ramsey is not responsible for any costs including, but not limited to, those incurred as a result of lost profits or revenue, loss of use of data, the costs of recovering such programs or data, the cost of any substitute programs or data, claims by third parties, or for other similar costs.</distliab><stdorder><ordering>This data set is distributed on the internet by clicking below after Online Linkage.</ordering></stdorder><distrib><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20190612</metd><metstdn>Minnesota Geographic Metadata Guidelines</metstdn><metstdv>1.2</metstdv><metextns><onlink>http://www.mngeo.state.mn.us/committee/standards/mgmg/metadata.htm</onlink></metextns><metc><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></metc></metainfo><spref><horizsys><planar><gridsys><gridsysn>Universal Transverse Mercator</gridsysn><utm><utmzone>15</utmzone></utm></gridsys><planci><plandu>meters</plandu></planci></planar><geodetic><horizdn>NAD83</horizdn><ellips>GRS80</ellips></geodetic></horizsys></spref></metadata>