<?xml version="1.0"?><metadata><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><title>ECC Dispatch Areas, Ramsey County, Minnesota</title><pubinfo><publish>Ramsey County Enterprise GIS</publish></pubinfo><pubdate>20190612</pubdate><origin>Ramsey County</origin><onlink>https://gisdata.mn.gov/dataset/us-mn-co-ramsey-bdry-admin-boundary-data</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>This dataset contains polygons that represent areas for dispatching law enforcement, fire and emergency medical services by Ramsey County Emergency Communications. The polygons match the vendor specific hierarchy, in the computer aided dispatch system used by Ramsey County Emergency Communications.</abstract><purpose>This data set is specially supports a better understanding of the open data published by the County related to emergency communications dispatch.</purpose><supplinf>Ramsey County</supplinf></descript><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>As needed</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-93.313180488</westbc><eastbc>-92.858547045</eastbc><northbc>45.324983751</northbc><southbc>44.699861062</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><theme><themekey>boundaries, computer aided dispatch areas, battalion, law enforcement, fire and emergency medical services</themekey><themekt>ISO Topic Category 19115</themekt></theme><place><placekey>Minnesota, MN, Ramsey County</placekey></place></keywords><accconst>None.</accconst><useconst>None. Please check sources, scale, accuracy, currentness and other available information. Please confirm that you are using the most recent copy of both data and metadata.  Acknowledgment of the publisher would be appreciated.</useconst><timeperd><timeinfo><sngdate><caldate>20190513</caldate></sngdate></timeinfo><current>The dataset is current and complete, but regularly updated to reflect changes.  New versions are released monthly.</current></timeperd><browse><browsen>None Available</browsen></browse><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac></idinfo><distinfo><distliab>EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY STATED HEREIN, THIS DATA IS PROVIDED AS IS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. USER BEARS ANY AND ALL RISK RELATING TO QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THIS DATA. 
Limit on Liability:  This data is not a legally recorded map or survey and is not intended to be used as one. This data is a compilation of records and information from various state, county, and city offices, and other sources, and should be used for reference only.
In no event will the County of Ramsey be liable for direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages arising out of the use of, or inability to use, the data, even if advised of the possibility of such damages.  Specifically, the County of Ramsey is not responsible for any costs including, but not limited to, those incurred as a result of lost profits or revenue, loss of use of data, the costs of recovering such programs or data, the cost of any substitute programs or data, claims by third parties, or for other similar costs.</distliab><resdesc>ISvSQL75.GISWarehouse.Other.ADMIN_DispatchArea</resdesc><stdorder><ordering>This data set is distributed on the internet by clicking below after Online Linkage.</ordering></stdorder><distrib><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20190612</metd><metstdn>Minnesota Geographic Metadata Guidelines</metstdn><metstdv>1.2</metstdv><metextns><onlink>http://www.mngeo.state.mn.us/committee/standards/mgmg/metadata.htm</onlink></metextns><metc><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></metc></metainfo><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>bdry_dispatcharea</enttypl></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>BattalionCode</attrlabl><attrdef>Alpha-Numeric value assigned to each Battalion</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>Battalion</attrlabl><attrdef>The lowest level in the Computer Aided Dispatch hierarchy</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>Division</attrlabl><attrdef>The Division area of a public safety agency</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>Jurisdiction</attrlabl><attrdef>The public safety agency responsible for Law Enforcement, Fire Service or Emergency Medical Services</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>Agency</attrlabl><attrdef>The Computer Aided Dispatch agencey, either Law Enforcement or Fire and Emergency Medical Service</attrdef></attr></detailed><overview><eaover>This polygon data set specifically supports data published by Ramsey County Emergency Communications Center (RC ECC), on Ramsey Countys Open Data Portal. Each polygon represents an area for aggregating 9-1-1 incident locations. The categorization of these areas is specific to the Computer Aided Dispatch software vendor utilized by the RC ECC.</eaover><eadetcit>Ramsey County Emergency Communications Center (RC ECC)</eadetcit></overview></eainfo><dataqual><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>Digitized information is generally +/- 7 feet; some areas have been found to be +/- 30 feet.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><attracc><attraccr>These areas represent where an incident was geo validated, and in most cases the public safety agency that responded to the incident.</attraccr></attracc><complete>Coverage Ramsey County Emergency Communications Dispatch and PSAP serving Areas</complete><lineage><procstep><procdesc>Created by Ramsey County Emergency Communications with consultation from the Public Safety agencies serving in Ramsey County.</procdesc></procstep></lineage><logic>Information is visually inspected and corrected as necessary.</logic></dataqual><spref><horizsys><planar><gridsys><gridsysn>Universal Transverse Mercator</gridsysn><utm><utmzone>15</utmzone></utm></gridsys><planci><plandu>meters</plandu></planci></planar><geodetic><horizdn>NAD83</horizdn><ellips>GRS80</ellips></geodetic></horizsys></spref></metadata>