<?xml version="1.0"?><metadata><eainfo><detailed><enttyp><enttypl>ADMIN_Precinct</enttypl></enttyp><attr><attrlabl>Precinct</attrlabl><attrdef>Precinct name (City Name P-1)</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>MCD</attrlabl><attrdef>Municipality where precinct is located</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>ShortLabel</attrlabl><attrdef>Precinct name without municipality (ex, P-1)</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>LongLabel</attrlabl><attrdef>Precinct name without municipality (ex, PRECINCT 1)</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>County</attrlabl><attrdef>County where precinct is located</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>LEG</attrlabl><attrdef>State Legislative District where the precinct is located</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>SEN</attrlabl><attrdef>State Senate boundary within which the precinct is located</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>JUD</attrlabl><attrdef>Judicial District where the precinct is located</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>Precinct_N</attrlabl><attrdef>Identifying code for the precinct from the statewide voter registration system</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>VR_MCD</attrlabl><attrdef>Municipality code for the precinct from the statewide voter registration system</attrdef></attr><attr><attrlabl>CTU_Code</attrlabl><attrdef>City, township, and unorganized territory unique ID for the precinct from the Minnesota Geospatial Information Office</attrdef></attr></detailed></eainfo><idinfo><citation><citeinfo><origin>Ramsey County</origin><title>Election Precincts, Ramsey County, Minnesota</title><pubinfo><publish>Ramsey County Enterprise GIS</publish></pubinfo><pubdate>20190627</pubdate><onlink>https://gisdata.mn.gov/dataset/us-mn-co-ramsey-bdry-admin-boundary-data</onlink></citeinfo></citation><descript><abstract>This data set contains polygons that represent Ramsey County Precincts as of the redistricting process following the 2010 census. Since the 2010 census some precincts boundaries have been updated in Little Canada, Maplewood, New Brighton, and St Paul as directed by city resolutions.</abstract><purpose>Precincts are often used as boundaries for analyzing other GIS data, including election districts, census data, tax data, and county services.</purpose><supplinf>Ramsey County</supplinf></descript><timeperd><current>Data set is complete, but irregularly being updated.</current><timeinfo><sngdate><caldate>Publication Date</caldate></sngdate></timeinfo></timeperd><status><progress>Complete</progress><update>Irregular</update></status><spdom><bounding><westbc>-93.228202</westbc><eastbc>-92.982974 </eastbc><northbc>45.124277</northbc><southbc>44.890922</southbc></bounding></spdom><keywords><place><placekey>Minnesota, MN, Ramsey County</placekey></place><theme><themekt>ISO Topic Category 19115</themekt><themekey>boundaries, elections, precincts</themekey></theme></keywords><accconst>None.</accconst><useconst>None. Please check sources, scale, accuracy, currentness and other available information. Please confirm that you are using the most recent copy of both data and metadata.  Acknowledgement of the publisher would be appreciated.</useconst><ptcontac><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></ptcontac></idinfo><dataqual><logic>Graphical elements are topologically clean. Over shoots and undershoots are not permitted. Parcel gaps and overlaps are analyzed in a case by case basis. Generally boundaries conflicting in position by less than 1 foot are dissolved into a single line giving precedence to Senior and Junior property boundaries</logic><complete>Entire Ramsey County Coverage</complete><posacc><horizpa><horizpar>Digitized information is generally +/- 7 feet; some areas have been found to be +/- 30 feet. COGO (coordinate geometry) accuracy generally is +/- 1.0 foot.</horizpar></horizpa></posacc><attracc><attraccr>Attributes are populated from a compilation of records and information from various state, county and city offices, and other sources. Accuracy may vary by source, but domains are used wherever possible to increase accuracy.</attraccr></attracc><lineage><procstep><procdesc>The Ramsey County Precincts were created as part of a redistricting process following the 2010 census and subsequent city resolutions.</procdesc></procstep></lineage></dataqual><distinfo><resdesc>ISvSQL75.GISWarehouse.Cadastral.ADMIN_Precincts</resdesc><distliab>EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY STATED HEREIN, THIS DATA IS PROVIDED AS IS WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. USER BEARS ANY AND ALL RISK RELATING TO QUALITY AND PERFORMANCE OF THIS DATA. 
Limit on Liability:  This data is not a legally recorded map or survey and is not intended to be used as one. This data is a compilation of records and information from various state, county, and city offices, and other sources, and should be used for reference only.
In no event will the County of Ramsey be liable for direct, indirect, special, incidental, or consequential damages arising out of the use of, or inability to use, the data, even if advised of the possibility of such damages.  Specifically, the County of Ramsey is not responsible for any costs including, but not limited to, those incurred as a result of lost profits or revenue, loss of use of data, the costs of recovering such programs or data, the cost of any substitute programs or data, claims by third parties, or for other similar costs.</distliab><stdorder><ordering>This data set is distributed on the internet by clicking below after Online Linkage.</ordering></stdorder><distrib><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></distrib></distinfo><metainfo><metd>20190627</metd><metstdn>Minnesota Geographic Metadata Guidelines</metstdn><metstdv>1.2</metstdv><metextns><onlink>http://www.mngeo.state.mn.us/committee/standards/mgmg/metadata.htm</onlink></metextns><metc><cntinfo><cntperp><cntorg>Ramsey County</cntorg><cntper>Matt Koukol</cntper></cntperp><cntpos>GIS Manager</cntpos><cntaddr><address>121 7th Place E</address><address>Suite 2300</address><city>Saint Paul</city><state>MN</state><postal>55101</postal></cntaddr><cntvoice>651.266.3463</cntvoice><cntemail>RCGISMetaData@co.ramsey.mn.us</cntemail></cntinfo></metc></metainfo><spref><horizsys><planar><gridsys><gridsysn>Universal Transverse Mercator</gridsysn><utm><utmzone>15</utmzone></utm></gridsys><planci><plandu>meters</plandu></planci></planar><geodetic><horizdn>NAD83</horizdn><ellips>GRS80</ellips></geodetic></horizsys></spref></metadata>